I am sharing a simple cycle formula
that all those people who are 60 years or
above and whose retirement is approaching
or has already been completed, they should opt for immediate
Varshgaan i.e. Immediate Plan. All those
people who are on the threshold of 40 to 45, 50 or
55 years of age, who
know that I have 5
years or 10 years, 15 years or 20 years left in my job,
they should go for deferred i.e. annual of 80. So the main
fear is that
you too who are about to retire or have retired, will
need immediate pension support, that office will expect pension in the same way
and it will demand a huge support
and those who have time, who want to secure their old age, their security, their retirement by investing their
money, their
investment, their liquidity at one place for the next 5 years, 10 years, 15 years, should go
towards Effort.